Ross N. Reeves III

401 S Garfield St, Unit 9 Phone: (828) 337-2885

Denver, CO 80209 Email: rossnr3@gmail.com

Summary

General Manager with domestic and international experience in sales, operations, and financial management of technology services and consulting businesses. Cross industry knowledge derived from developing, selling and operating technology services for medium and large corporate customers, including financial services (investment banking, retail banking, thrifts, credit unions), healthcare (insurance, hospitals), energy (gas, electric utilities), telecommunications (carriers), and manufacturing (automotive).

Experience

January 2001 – Present Retired Denver, CO

Management of personal investments.

June 1988 – January 2001 Perot Systems Corporation Dallas, TX

Co-Founder, General Management, Director

- Served in various roles from sales and recruiting during the early phases of the start-up to general management roles involving corporate operations both domestically and internationally as the company evolved.
- Involved in all aspects of growing the company from 8 employees with \$0 sales to 16,000 employees with annual sales of \$1.4 Billion during first 11 years, with an initial public offering in 1999.

June 1970 – June 1988 Electronic Data Systems Corporation Dallas, TX Executive Vice President of Technology Services, Corporate Officer

- Joined the company as a trainee in EDS' Systems Engineering Development Program.
- Involved in many projects consisting of the design, development, and implementation of systems for health care insurers, electric utilities, retail banks, thrifts, retailers and internal proprietary systems, progressing from systems engineer to various levels of technical project management.
- Managed all technology functions for the financial services industry segment of EDS and provided sales support for outsourcing and application development services.
- Managed EDS' internal proprietary applications development and support, and responsible for contracting for all acquired technology equipment, software and services.
- Managed EDS' technology infrastructure, consolidating decentralized processing centers and networks into a centralized infrastructure supporting all U.S. and European clients.
- Made an officer of the corporation in 1982. EDS was acquired by General Motors in 1984.
- Responsible for merging the global technology infrastructures of EDS and GM, and operating and pricing all customer contracts involving 16 currencies.

June 1966 – June 1970 U.S. Marine Corps Company Commander, Captain

 Served tours at Marine Barracks, 8th and I, Washington, D.C.; Republic of South Vietnam; and USMC Basic School, Quantico, VA.

Education

1966 U.S. Naval Academy Annapolis, MD

BS, Engineering

1995 Harvard Business School Cambridge, MA

• MBA, Advanced Management Program